Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory4 Mss.B.B61.inventory04
American Philosophical Society
Franz Boas Papers: Inventory (D)
1862-1942
Mss.B.B61.inventory04
American Philosophical Society
1.0 section
This is part of the large inventory for the Franz Boas Papers (Mss B B61). For complete information concerning this collection, please view the Collection Description.
Boas, Franz, 1858-1942
Scope and Contents note
Due to the size of the collection, the content for Series I has been divided into multiple inventories. Please follow the links below to browse the inventories.
Inventories
Correspondents A
Correspondents B
Correspondents C
Correspondents D
Correspondents E-G
Correspondents H
Correspondents I-K
Correspondents L
Correspondents M
Correspondents N-Q
Correspondents R
Correspondents S
Correspondents T-V
Correspondents W-Z
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents D
  - D., G.A. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1910 July 8
  - Dabb, Edith Manville (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1927 May 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 24; 2p
  - Dabbs, J. Autray (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1937 July 25; 1p
  - Dabkowski, P. von (Box 19)
    - 1927 Mat 4
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 27; 1p
      - bibliog. enc., 1927 May 27; 2p
  - Dabney, C.W. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 27
  - Dabney, Thomas L. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 June 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1925 June 25; 2p
  - Dahlberg, E. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 13; 1p
  - Dahlberg, Gunnar (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1943 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 5
  - Daily Mirror, Editor (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 19; 1p
      Scope and Contents note
      enc. with FB to Fraenkel, O.
  - Daily, Dr. Ray K. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 6; 1p
  - Dala (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1899 Mar. 13
  - Dale, Edgar (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 10; 1p
  - Dale, Harry S. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1940 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 3; 1p
  - Dale, J.T. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 29; 1p
  - Daley, M. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 26; 1p
  - Dall, Wm. H. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1886 Oct. 16
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 21; 1p
  - Dalland, J. (Box 19)
    - From Franco, E., 1930 July 1; 1p
    - See Uhle, Max, 1933 June 30
  - Dallenbach, K.M. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 9; 1p
  - Daly, Charles P. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1884 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1884 Nov. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 12; 2p
  - Daly, Judge Charles P. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1896 Mar. 12
    - To Boas (see FB to Jacobi), 1896 Mar. 11
    - To Boas (see FB to Jacobi), 1897 Jan. 9
    - To Boas (see FB to Jacobi), 1898 Feb. 15
    - To Boas (see FB to Jacobi), 1898 Dec. 1
  - Dalzell, John W. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1891 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1891 Mar. 20
  - Dam, Cornelia (Mrs. Loring) (Box 19)
    - To Bos, 1938 Jan. 8; 1p
  - Dames [?], Bruno (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 14; 1p
  - Dampf, A. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 20; 2p
    - From Cattell, J.M., 1933 July 13
  - Damrosch, Frank (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1909 June 25; 1p
    - Boas to "walter", 1917 Feb. 1
      General note
      Damrosch but the address response are Frank Damrosch
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 2p
      Boas to Dixon, 10 Dec 1909, on reverse
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 19; 1p
  - Damrosch, Hetty (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 11; 4p
  - Damrosch, Walter (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 1
      (mistakenly used "walter" through the address response are Frank Damrosch - see entry above)
  - Dan (Box 19)
    See Cranmer, Dan
  - Dana, E.S. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 16; 1
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 8; 1p
  - Danckelmann, A. von (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 31
    - To Boas, 1889 June 19
    - To Boas, [undated - Feb. or June?]
  - Danforth, Allen (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1901 June 3; 1p
  - Danforth, C.H. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 1; 1p
      - [with enc.:], 1931 June 29; 1p
    - CHD -- to Guthe, C.E., 1931 June 29
    - CHD -- to Gregory, W.K., 1931 June 29
    - CHD -- to Blom, F., 1931 June 29
    - CHD -- to Scammon, R.E., 1931 June 29
    - To Boas, 1931 July 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 14; 1p
    - CHD -- to Blom, F.
    - CHD -- to Gregory, W.K., 1931 July 8
  - Daniels, E.D. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 13; 1p
  - Daniels, Geo. F. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1891 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1891 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1891 Feb. 17
  - Daniels, Josephus (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 7; 1p
  - Danielson, C.S., Bursar, Columbia U. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1915 May 28
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 3
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 14
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - From Boas, 1916 June 9
    - From Boas, 1916 June 23
    - From Boas, 1916 Sep. 28
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 20
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 28
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1917 June 1
    - From Boas, 1917 June 13
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 17
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9, Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 7, 1920 Sep. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 July 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1916 May 26
    - To Boas, 1916 June 1
    - To Boas, 1916 July 27, July 31
    - To Boas, 1916 July Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1916 July Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1917 May 22
    - To Boas, 1917 June 27
    - To Boas, 1917 June 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 June 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 7; 1p
    - CSD -- from Barrett, G.H., 1912 July 10
  - Dannehl, A. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 18; 1p
  - Dannemann, Edouardo (Box 19)
    - To Bilden, R., 1933 Nov. 18; 1p
  - Dannick, Fred L. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 9; 1p
  - Danton, G.H. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 My 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 21; 1p
  - Danzel, Hedwig (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1928 June 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 5; 2p
  - Danzel, Richard (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 6; 3p
  - Danzel, Theodor W. -- [also see below] (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1928 Jne 23; 1p
  - Danzel, Theodor-Wilhelm -- [also see above] (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 16; 5p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 July 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 Sep. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 12; 2p
      - see Danzel, Hedwig, 1928 June 23
  - Danzig. Bücherei der Königlichen Technischen Hochschule (Box 19)
    See Trommsdorff, Paul
  - Danziger, Ernst (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 1p
    - ED -- to Heuser, F.W., 1923 Feb. 13; 1pand
      - enc. Schwalbe, J. to Einhorn, 1923 Jan. 17
  - Darby, George E. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1929 May 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 July 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 10; 1p
  - Darby, S.E. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 31; 2p
  - Darton, N.H. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 3; 1p
  - Darwin, Francis (Box 19)
    - From DF to Boas, 1909 Mar. 9
  - Dashiell, John F. (Box 19)
    - See FB open letter, Spain, replies, 1938 Jan.
  - Date, W.E. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1918 June 8; 1p
  - Daub, Allen L. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 16; 1p
  - Dauber & Pine Bookshops (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 7; 1p
  - Daugherty, D.H. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Dec. 11; 1p
  - Dávalos, Baldino (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1918 May 24; 1p
    - To N.M. Butler, 1906 July 2; 2p
  - Davenport, Charles B. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1909 May 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Nov. 20
    - From Boas, 1924 June 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 May 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 May 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 24; 1p
    - To Hrdlicka, A., 1927 May 18; 1p
  - David (Box 19)
    - To Dunn, L.C., 1938 June 21; 2p
  - David, E.M. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Aug. 31; 1p
  - David?, Friedrich (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1932 May 3; 2p
  - Davidsen, A. (i.e. H.C. Davidsen) (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 3p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 9; 6p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 23; 2p
  - Davidson, A.A. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Goddard, P.E., 1926 Aug. 30; 1p
    - To Goddard, P.E., 1927 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Goddard, P.E., 1927 Feb. 3
  - Davidson, C.S. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1917 June 22
  - Davidson, H.P. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1917 May 21
  - Davidson, Israel (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 15; 1p
  - Davidson, M.P. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Picker, J., 1933 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Picker, J., 1933 Dec. 16
  - Davidson, Robert (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1936 July 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 17; 1p
  - Davies, C.E. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 5; 1p
      - co-signers: Morrow, L.W.
      - ?Free, E.E.
  - Davies, D.C. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1922 Oct. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Dec. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 May 15
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 5; 1p
  - Davies, Jos. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1942 June 4; 3p
  - Davila, Victor M. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 24; 2p
  - Davis (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 1
  - Davis, Andrew W.J. (Box 19)
    - 1908 Apr. 16, 1p
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 2
  - Davis, Allen J. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 23; 1p
  - Davis, B. Colwell (Box 19)
    - From Finkelstein, M.I., 1939 Oct. 31
  - Davis, D. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1905 May 9; 2p
  - Davis, Hallowell (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 19; 1p
  - Davis, H.C. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 27
  - Davis, H.T. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 24; 1p
  - Davis, J. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 19; 1p
  - Davis, J.E. (Box 19)
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 May 5
  - Davis, Jerome (Box 19)
    - see Boas, F., open letter, re Spain, 1938 Jan.
  - Davis, J.J.? (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 2p
    - To Prince, J.D., 1929 Dec. 14; 1p
  - Davis, John K. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 13; 1p
  - Davis, J.W. (Box 19)
    - From Boas, 1933 July 24; 1p
  - Davis, Marian (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1936 June 14; 1p
  - Davis, Michael E. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 19
    - To Boas, E.P., 1942 Dec. 22; 1p
  - Davis, Michael M., Jr. (Box 20)
    - To Boas [?], 1911 June 1; 2p
  - Davis, Norman H. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1940 June 10; 1p
  - Davis, Royal J. (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 18; 1p
  - Davis, Watson (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Sep. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1931 June 24; 1p
      - Radio talk [?], 1931 June; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Bryan, R.W., 1931 Jan. 8; 1p
  - Davis, Wm. Harper (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1905 May 11
  - Davis-Dubois, Rachel (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 5; 2p
  - Davisson, C.J. (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 7; 1p
  - Dawson, George M. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1886 Dec. 11; 3p
    - From Boas, 1888 [no date ca. Nov. 28]; 1p
    - From Boas, 1889 Nov. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1890 Dec. 20, 1891 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1894 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1894 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1894 May 15
    - From Boas, 1894 Sep. 21
    - From Boas, 1898 June 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1896 June 4
    - To Boas, 1886 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1886 July 28
    - To Boas, 1886 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1886 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1886 Aug. 27; 6p
    - To Boas, 1886 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1886 Nov. 28
    - To Boas, 1886 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1886 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1887 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1887 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 15, Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 18
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr. 39
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 9, Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1888 Mar. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 May 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1888 May 17
    - To Boas, 1888 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 June 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 July 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1888 Nov. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1888 ca. Nov. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 4; 4p
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 Feb. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1889 Feb. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1889 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1889 Apr. 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1889 May 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 May 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 July 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1889 July 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 Aug. 4, Aug. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1890 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1890 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1890 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1890 May 3
    - To Boas, 1890 May 30
    - To Boas, 1890 June 16
    - To Boas, 1890 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1890 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1890 Dec. 10
    - To Boas [2], 1890 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1890 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1891 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1891 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1891 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1894 May 11
    - To Boas, 1894 May 15
    - To Boas, 1894 May 28
    - To Boas, 1894 June 5
    - To Boas, 1894 June 15
    - To Boas, 1894 June 22
    - To Boas, 1894 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar 15 and Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1895 June 5
    - To Boas, 1895 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1895 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 6
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1896 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1896 May 11
    - To Boas, 1896 May 25
    - To Boas, 1896 June 4
    - To Boas, 1896 June 12
    - To Boas, 1896 July 3
    - To Boas, 1896 July 4
    - To Boas, 1896 July 14
    - To Boas, 1896 July 18
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 24
    - To Boas, 1896 Sep. 1
    - To Boas, 1896 Sep. 14
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1897 Feb. 11, Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1897 July 10
    - To Boas, 1897 Aug. 7
    - To Boas, 1897 Aug. 26
    - To Boas, 1897 Oct. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1897 Nov. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 28, Mar. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 June 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 July 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Hale, Horatio, 1888
  - Day, A.L. (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p
    - From Clark, A.H., 1931 May 19
      - enc. with Roos, C.F., 1931 May 20
  - Day, E.E. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 June 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1932 June 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1932 July 17; 3p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 3; 1p
    - To Butler, N.M., 1932 Apr. 7; 1p
    - To Butler, N.M., 1933 Mar. 1; 1p
    - To McBain, H.L., 1934 Feb. 10; 1p
  - Day, Miss (Box 20)
    - From Wessel, B.B. (Mrs. M.J.), 1925 Feb. 27
      - enc. with Wessel, 1925 Mar. 5
  - Day, R.R. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 20; 1p
  - Dayton, Neil A. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Sep. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 23; 1p
    - From Klopfer, Bruno, 1936 Oct. 12
  - Dealy (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 4
  - Dean, Bashford (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1910 June 7
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 Sep. 22
  - Deans, James (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1894 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1894 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1894 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 2; 4p
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1896 Apr. 7
  - Dearborn, Ned H. (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 May 20; 1p
      - also to Malisoff, W.M. Patterson, E.M., 1940 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 16; 1p
      - see Rautenstrauch, W., 1941 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1934 May?; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 11; 1p
      - Morris, N., 1938 Sep. 24; 1p
      - co-signed: Rodman, S.J.
      - Kern, P.J.
    - To Boas, 1941 July 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 25; 1p
      - see Boas, F., co-signer, 1941 Oct. 25; 1
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Aug. 13; 1p
      - open letter, 1942 May?; 1p
    - To Amer. Comm. Dem. & Free., 1941 Nov. 5; 1p
      - see Boas, F. to Carlson, 1940 May 24
    - To Edel, Bertha C., 1940 Dec. 18; 1p
    - From Graham, Frank P., 1941 Aug. 11
    - N.Y. Times, Editor, 1941 Nov. 6; 3p
  - Deardorff. N.R. (Neva R.) (Box 20)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 10; 1p
  - Debenetti, Salvador (Box 20)
    - See Rivarola, Rodolfo, 1917 Aug. 31; ?
  - DeBra, A.H. (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 22; 1p
  - Decinos, A. (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1917 July 24
  - Deckert, E. (Box 20)
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 22; 4p
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1888 May 7; 4p